<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" 
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" 
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>jdmunger</title>
    <link>https://jdmunger.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on jdmunger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>am9obi5kLm11bmdlckBwcm90b25tYWlsLmNvbQo=(Base64 encoded) (John Munger)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>am9obi5kLm11bmdlckBwcm90b25tYWlsLmNvbQo=(Base64 encoded) (John Munger)</webMaster>
    <copyright>©2022, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:06:25 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://jdmunger.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      
      
      
        
      
        
      
        
      
        
      
        
      
        
      
        
      
        
      
        
      

      
      <item>
        <title>Friday Prayer</title>
        <link>https://jdmunger.com/posts/friday_prayer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:06:25 -0500</pubDate>
        <author>am9obi5kLm11bmdlckBwcm90b25tYWlsLmNvbQo=(Base64 encoded) (John Munger)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:06:25 -0500</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://jdmunger.com/posts/friday_prayer/</guid>
        <description>Its Friday, July 29th, 2022. I&amp;rsquo;m a little sad. I&amp;rsquo;m worn out from a week&amp;rsquo;s worth of fighting with myself, a week&amp;rsquo;s worth of attempting to marshall myself to get meaningful work done, a week&amp;rsquo;s worth of small victories and defeats, a week&amp;rsquo;s worth of good days and bad days, a week&amp;rsquo;s worth of reaching out to friends over text, and most of us being too busy or tired from work to respond to each other.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>John Munger</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
          
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Meal Plans</title>
        <link>https://jdmunger.com/posts/meal-plan/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 15:42:23 -0500</pubDate>
        <author>am9obi5kLm11bmdlckBwcm90b25tYWlsLmNvbQo=(Base64 encoded) (John Munger)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 15:42:23 -0500</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://jdmunger.com/posts/meal-plan/</guid>
        <description>Meal Planning Rather than opining and getting grandiose, I&amp;rsquo;ll quickly explain my reasoning behind my meal planning, what i&amp;rsquo;m aiming for, and the items on the list.
The inspiration is simple. I&amp;rsquo;ve been experimenting for the past couple of years in the vegan/vegetarian recipe space, and, at this point, I spend too much time improvising, and reacting. I want a more targetted, more intentionally nutritionally balanced meals, and a plan. Having a plan saves time and effort, and I need a more explicit default setting.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>John Munger</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>food</category>
            
          
            
              <category>order</category>
            
          
        
        
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
          
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Schedule</title>
        <link>https://jdmunger.com/lowkey/schedule/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>am9obi5kLm11bmdlckBwcm90b25tYWlsLmNvbQo=(Base64 encoded) (John Munger)</author>
        
        <guid>https://jdmunger.com/lowkey/schedule/</guid>
        <description>Reminder The point of this schedule is to make a schedule that&amp;rsquo;s fun, not to optimize
Remember to take a breathe when you are overwhelmed Remind yourself how you&amp;rsquo;ll feel after these activities Monday Before Work: Start Laundry Project Afterwork: Fitbod Fold Laundry Read Tuesday Before Work: Dishes Japanese Brilliant Afterwork: Game Project Wednesday Before Work: Japanese Brilliant Afterwork: FitBod Game Read Thursday Before Work: Japanese Brilliant Call The Oaks Afterwork: FitBod Game Project Friday Before Work: Project Afterwork: Friends Tim &amp;amp; Mimsy Date Night Saturday Morning golf something else Afternoon Criterion Channel Evening Free Sunday Morning F1 Afternoon Board Games Evening Prepare for the week Options Education Busuu &amp;amp; Wanikani Brilliant Reading Audiobooks Criterion Movie Physical Fitness Golf FitBod Workouts Family and Friends Dishes Laundry Date Night Quality time with Christina Quality time with friends Creation Blogging Personal Software Development (Hugo sites, and Full Stack) Drums Entertainment Video Games Board Games </description>
        
        <dc:creator>John Munger</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
          
        
      </item>
      

    
  </channel>
</rss>
